A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, Speeches, Series 33 FA372
Rockefeller Archive Center
Nelson A. Rockefeller gubernatorial records, Speeches, Series 33
1958-1973
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich)
FA372
97 Record Cartons
Biographical/Historical note
Nelson A. Rockefeller served as governor of New York from January 1, 1959, to December 18, 1973. He was the first person elected to four consecutive four-year terms as a state governor.
File Plan note
Former Classification: III 15 33
Conditions Governing Access note
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Scope and Contents note
This series contains Rockefeller's reading copy of speeches and transcripts of his remarks at press conferences. Some files contain drafts of speeches. Broad topics include both New York state and national government, politics, and public policy issues. Also included are speeches he made during his campaigns for the Republican presidential nomination in 1960, 1964, and 1968.
Arrangement note
This series is arranged chronologically.
Other Finding Aids note
Detailed finding aids for each series of this collection are available:
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Appointments Office (FA353)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Assembly and Senate Memos (FA354)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Joseph H. Boyd (FA355)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, James Cannon (FA356)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Affirmative Action (N. Lee Cook) (FA357)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Counsel's Office (FA358)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, New York State Committee to Reelect the President (FA359)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Jerry A. Danzig (FA360)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Executive Chamber (FA361)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, 55th Street (FA362)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Issue Books (FA363)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Arthur Massolo (FA364)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Hugh Morrow (FA242)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, New York Office (FA365)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Civil Service Resolutions (Charles H. Palmer) (FA366)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Political Files (FA367)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Press Office (FA368)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Public Relations (FA369)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Departmental Reports (FA370)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, William J. Ronan (FA371)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Diane Van Wie (FA373)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Ann C. Whitman, Gubernatorial (FA374)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Gene Wyckoff (FA375)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, New York Republican State Fund Raising Reports (FA376)
Affirmative action programs -- New York (State); Arms control; Arms control -- United States; Civil defense; International relations; International economic relations; Human rights; Governors -- Election -- New York (State) -- 1970; New York (N.Y.); Legislation -- New York (State); Latin America; International relations -- United States; Presidential campaigns -- United States; Political science; Political campaigns -- United States; New York (State); Vice-Presidents -- United States; United States; State governments -- United States; Public relations; Public policy; Presidential candidates -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Governors -- Election -- New York (State) -- 1966; Governors -- Election -- New York (State) -- 1962; Governors -- Election -- New York (State) -- 1958; Government policy; Federal government -- United States; Economics; Civil service -- New York (State); Civil service; Civil defense -- United States
- NAR Acceptance Speech for Republican Nomination for Governor - War Memorial Auditorium, Rochester, New York, August 25, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign Speeches, August 25-November 3, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- NAR's Inaugural Address, January 1, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Message of Governor Nelson A. Rockefeller to the Legislature, January 2, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Speeches, September 1959 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- State Fair - Syracuse, New York, September 10, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Southwest Manufacturing Company, a Division of Standard Railway Equipment Company - Amsterdam, New York, September 17, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Scope and Contents note
  Opening ceremony for new branch.
- Henry Hudson Planetarium Ground-breaking - Albany, New York, September 19, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Temple Shaaray Tefila Dedication - New York City, September 20, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Mortgage Bankers Association - New York City, September 21, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Saints and Sinner Luncheon - New York, September 22, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- United Jewish Appeal - Joint Defense Appeal Dinner - New York City, September 22, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Governor's Fire Prevention Conference - Open Meeting - Albany, New York, September 24, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Long Island Daily Press - Distinguished Service Award Dinner - Garden City, Long Island, New York, September 24, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Associated Industries of New York State - Whiteface Inn, September 25, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- International Association of the Chiefs of Police - New York City, September 28, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- New York University - Bellevue Medical Center Ground-breaking- New York City, September 28, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- County Officers Association - Grossingers, New York, September 28, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- New York State Civil Defense Commission - Civil Defense Directors - Grossingers, New York, September 28, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- National Fund for Medical Education - Joseph Devereaux Award Dinner - New York City, September 29, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Magazine Publishers Association, Inc. - Luncheon - New York City, September 29, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Federation of Jewish Philanthropies - New York City, September 29, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Community Service Society - Fund Raising Campaign - New York City, September 30, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Speeches, October 1959 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Court of Appeals - Albany, New York, October 5, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  Opening of building, dinner at Mansion.
- General Electric Company - Albany, New York, October 5, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  Luncheon with managers at University Club.
- Pulaski Memorial Committee - New York City, October 4, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  Review parade, dinner.
- 1960 White House Conference on Children and Youth - Albany, New York, October 5, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Dinner in Honor of Prime Minister Segni of Italy - Italo-American Committee - New York City, October 4, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Regional Planning Association - Conference and Luncheon - New York City, October 7, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- New York Board of Trade - Annual Gold Awards Dinner - New York City., October 8, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Governor's Committee on Employing the Physically Handicapped - Annual Meeting - New York City, October 9, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Columbus Day Dinner - Columbus Citizens Committee - New York City, October 12, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  Review Columbus Day Parade.
- Grand Chapter, State of New York Order of the Eastern Star - New York City, October 14, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Council of Greater New York Girl Scouts - New York City, October 14, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Investment Bankers Association - New York City, October 14, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- American Public Health Association - Atlantic City, New Jersey, October 19, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Inland Daily Press Association, October 20, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Not Used (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Young Women's Christian Association - Annual Luncheon - New York City, October 21, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- New York State Parents and Teachers Association - Annual Convention - Albany, New York, October 21, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Society of Foreign Consuls - New York City, October 22, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Alfred E. Smith Memorial Foundation, Inc. - Annual Dinner - New York City, October 22, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- World's Fair Committee - Washington, D.C., October 23, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Cayuga County Republican Committee - Auburn, New York, October 26, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Bristol Research Laboratories - Dedication of New Research Building - Syracuse, New York, October 26, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Northway - Opening of First Section - Albany, New York, October 27, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- New York State School Boards Association, Inc. - Annual Convention - Syracuse, New York, October 26, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- State Police - Dedication of Troup "G" Headquarters - Loudonville, New York, October 27, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Governor's Council on Rehabilitation - Albany, New York, October 29, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  NAR did not actually speak.
- Emmanuel Baptist Church - 125th Anniversary Dinner - Albany, New York, October 29, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Man of the Year Dinner - Tarrytown Chamber of Commerce - Tarrytown, New York, October 30, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- State University of New York, Albany - Installation of Hamilton as President - Albany, New York, October 29, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Wind-Up Dinner - Eastchester Republican Committee - Tuckahoe, New York, October 31, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Speeches, November 1959 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Federation of Protestant Welfare Agencies - New York City, November 5, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- United Neighborhood Houses - Luncheon - New York City, November 9, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Economic Club of New York - New York City, November 10, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- National Conference of Christians and Jews - Dinner - New York City, November 11, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- West Coast Trip - Miscellaneous, November 12-15, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 60)
- World Affairs Council - Luncheon - Los Angeles, California, November 12, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 61)
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - New York State Convention - Buffalo, New York, November 16, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 62)
- Western States Republican Conference - Los Angeles, California, November 12, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  Joint meeting with Western States Women Republicans,, T.
- Data on California (Western) Trip, November 12-15, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 64)
- Press Club - San Francisco, California, November 13, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  Joint luncheon with Union League Club and Commonwealth Club of California.
- Western States Republican Conference - Los Angeles, California, November 13, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 66)
- University of Oregon - Convocation of Students, Faculty and Public - Eugene, Oregon, November 14, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Willamette University - Salem, Oregon, November 14, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Freedom House - 18th Anniversary Dinner to Present Annual Freedom Award to Dr. Paul-Henri Spaak - New York City, November 16, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 69)
- Museum of Modern Art - New York City, November 16, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  Fund-raising opening, speak.
- American Legion - Installation of Martin B. McKneally as National Commander - New York City, November 19, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 71)
- Women's National Republican Club - "Salute to Rockefeller" Gala - New York City, November 19, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 72)
- National Foreign Trade Council - World Trade Dinner - New York City, November 18, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 73)
- New England Society of Newspaper Editors - Providence, Rhode Island, November 20, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 74)
- Rhode Island State Republican Committee - Luncheon - Providence, Rhode Island, November 20, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 75)
- NAR Midwest Trip, December 1959 (Box 2, Folder 76)
- Little White House Conference on Aging - New York City, December 1, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 77)
- New York State Civil Defense Commission - Women's Civil Defense Seminar - New York City, December 3, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 78)
- New York Bible Society - 150th Anniversary Dinner - New York City, December 4, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 79)
- National Conference of State Legislative Leaders - Albany, New York, December 7, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  Reception at mansion and dinner at Ten Eyck.
- New York State Republican Committee - Dinner Honoring Jane Todd - New York City, December 9, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 81)
- Data on Mid-Western Trip, December 1959 (Box 2, Folder 82)
- Northern Indiana Party Workers - South Bend, Indiana, December 12, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 83)
- Republican Fund-Raising Dinner - South Bend, Indiana, December 12, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 84)
- Republican Organization Tea - St. Louis, Missouri, December 13, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 85)
- Statement: Labor-Management - South Bend, Indiana, December 13, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 86)
- St. Louis Area Businessmen's Dinner - St. Louis, Missouri, December 13, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 87)
- Fund Raising Lunch for New Jewish Center - St. Louis, Missouri, December 13, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 88)
- St. Paul Republican Business Leaders - St. Paul, Minnesota, December 14, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 89)
- American-Swedish Institute - Reception - Minneapolis, Minnesota, December 14, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 90)
- Ramsey County Republican Committee and Minnesota Republican State Committee - Joint Luncheon - St. Paul, Minnesota, December 14, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 91)
- Dane County Republican Committee - Republican Members of Legislature - Joint Reception - Madison, Wisconsin, December 15, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 92)
- Milwaukee County Republican Committee - Luncheon - Milwaukee, Wisconsin, December 15, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 93)
- Minneapolis Junior Chamber of Commerce - Minneapolis, Minnesota, December 14, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 94)
- Reception and Fund-Raising Party - Oklahoma City, Oklahoma, December 16, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 95)
- Brown County Republican Committee - Breakfast - Green Bay, Wisconsin, December 16, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 96)
- Racine County Committee - Racine, Wisconsin, December 16, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 97)
- World Affairs Council - Dinner - Milwaukee, Wisconsin, December 15, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 98)
- Breakfast - Oklahoma City, Oklahoma, December 17, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 99)
- Press Club - Joint Luncheon with Dallas Council on World Affairs - Dallas, Texas, December 17, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 100)
- Houston, Texas, December 17, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 101)
- Republican Luncheon - Miami, Florida, December 18, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 102)
- Speeches, January 1960 (Box 2, Folder 103)
- New York State Women's Joint Legislative Forum - Albany, New York, January 12, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 104)
- New York State Agricultural Society - Annual Dinner - Albany, New York, January 13, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 105)
- Federation of American-Hellenic Societies of Greater New York - New York City, January 21, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 106)
- New York State Insurance Department - Centennial Dinner - New York City, January 21, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 107)
- White House Conference on Fallout Protection - Washington, D.C., January 25, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 108)
- District of Columbia Republican Committee - "Dinner with Ike" - Washington, D.C., January 27, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 109)
- Young Republicans, New York State - Albany, New York, January 29, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 110)
- Baseball Writers Association Dinner - New York City, January 31, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 111)
- Speeches, February 1960 (Box 2, Folder 112)
- Empire State Chamber of Commerce Dinner - Albany, New York, February 2, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 113)
- Association of the Fire Districts of New York State - New York City, February 9, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 114)
- Association of Towns of the State of New York - Luncheon - New York City, February 9, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 115)
- Osteopathic Society of the City of New York - New York City, February 10, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 116)
  Luncheon by Morris Morgenstern Foundation.
- Erie County Republican Finance Committee Dinner - Buffalo, New York, February 10, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 117)
- American Association of School Administrators - Atlantic City, New Jersey, February 14, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 118)
- League of Women Voters of New York - Legislative Conference - Albany, New York, February 16, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 119)
- New York Press Association - Annual Convention - Syracuse, New York, February 19, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 120)
- Second Reformed Church of Tarrytown - Washington's Birthday Dinner - Tarrytown, New York, February 24, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 121)
- Speeches, March 1960 (Box 2, Folder 122)
- New York State Association of Radio and Television Broadcasters - Albany, New York, March 1, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 123)
- New York State Federation of Women's Republican Clubs - Legislative Breakfast - Albany, New York, March 1, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 124)
- Young Women's Christian Association - Meeting of National Board of Directors - New York City, March 3, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 125)
- New York State Civil Defense Commission - Men's Civil Defense Seminar - New York City, March 4, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 126)
- New York State Civil Service Employees Association Dinner - Albany, New York, March 10, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 127)
- Legislative Correspondents Association - Dinner and Show - Albany, New York, March 12, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 128)
- United Jewish Appeal Dinner - New York City, March 16, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 129)
- Friendly Sons of St. Patrick - New York City, March 17, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 130)
- Boy Scouts - Capital Camp Campaign Breakfast - New York City, March 18, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 131)
- Speeches, April 1960 (Box 2, Folder 132)
- State University of New York, Jamestown Community College - Ground-breaking Ceremonies, April 7, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 133)
- Chautauqua County Republican Committee Dinner - Jamestown, New York, April 7, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 134)
- State University of New York, Stony Brook Community College - Ground-breaking Ceremonies, April 8, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 135)
- Dinner for President Lleras Camargo - New York City, April 11, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 136)
  NAR gave introduction.
- Kordite Corporation - Ground-breaking - Macedon, New York, April 13, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 137)
- Rochester Chamber of Commerce - Annual Pan American Day Luncheon - Rochester, New York, April 13, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 138)
- National Committee for Labor Israel - Dinner - New York City, April 16, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 139)
- Vassar College - Poughkeepsie, New York, April 18, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 140)
  NAR spoke to student group.
- Lycoming County Republican Committee - "Schneebeli for Congress" Luncheon - Williamsport, Pennsylvania, April 20, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 141)
- Ten Eyck Women's Council, New York State Department of Commerce - Luncheon - Albany, New York, April 21, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 142)
- Schneebeli-for-Congress Committee - Dinner - Wellsboro, Pennsylvania, April 20, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 143)
- World Affairs Council - Luncheon - Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, April 22, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 144)
- Franco-American Society - Dinner in Honor of French President DeGaulle - New York City, April 26, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 145)
- Luncheon for New York City County Chairman - New York City, April 27, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 146)
- Law Day - Albany, New York, April 29, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 147)
- Erie County Republican Finance Committee - Buffalo, New York, April 30, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 148)
- Speeches, May 1960 (Box 3, Folder 149)
- University of Chicago - Law Center Convocation - Chicago, Illinois, May 1, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 150)
- State of Israel 12th Anniversary of Independence - New York City, May 2, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 151)
- Local 32-B Building Service Employees International Union - Luncheon - New York City, May 2, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 152)
- Fordham University - Law School Cornerstone Ceremony - New York City, May 3, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 153)
- New York State Agricultural Experiment Station - Dedication of New Food Service and Technology Building - Geneva, New York, May 5, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 154)
- Willard State Hospital - Dedication of Plaque Commemorating First Agricultural College in U.S. - Ovid, New York, May 5, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 155)
- Geneva Chamber of Commerce - Dinner - Geneva, New York, May 5, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 156)
- State University Teachers College - Plattsburgh, New York, May 5, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 157)
- NAR - Geneva, New York, May 5-6, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 158)
- Events NAR Did Not Attend, May 15-20, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 159)
- Route 17 Association - Corning, New York, May 17, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 160)
- New General Electric Laboratory Groundbreaking - Schenectady, New York, May 19, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 161)
- State Education Building - Dedication of New Wing - Albany, New York, May 19, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 162)
- New York National Guard - Ground-breaking Ceremony for New Armory - Saranac Lake, New York, May 20, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 163)
- Adirondack Conservation Council - Reception and Dinner - Lake Placid, New York, May 20, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 164)
- Statement: Summit Conference Failure, May 23, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 165)
- African Methodist Episcopal Zion Church - Buffalo, New York, May 12, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 166)
- Norway's Constitution Day - Liev Eiriksson Park, Brooklyn, New York, May 15, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 167)
- Japan Society - Dinner in Honor of Former Prime Minister Shigeru Yoshida - New York City, May 23, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 168)
- Council on Foreign Relations - New York City, May 24, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 169)
- New York State Health Department - New York State Public Health Conference - New York City, May 24, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 170)
- Kiwanis - Inter-Club Service Luncheon - Lockport, New York, May 26, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 171)
- Pan American Award Assembly - Evander Childs High School, Bronx, New York, May 31, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 172)
- United Jewish Appeal - Luncheon - New York City, May 31, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 173)
- Speeches, June 1960 (Box 3, Folder 174)
- Automation Conference - Cooperstown, New York, June 1, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 175)
- Holstein-Fresian Association - Syracuse, New York, June 1, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 176)
- Statement: Economic Growth, June 1, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 177)
- North Dakota Trip, June 1960 (Box 3, Folder 178)
- NAR - Cooperstown, June 1-3, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 179)
- TV - Air Defense Alert, June 2, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 180)
- New York State Lions Club - Convention - South Fallsburgh, New York, June 6, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 181)
- TV Recording on Camp Thacher, June 7, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 182)
- Conference of Office of Local Government - Albany, New York, June 7, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 183)
- NAR Statement: Challenge to Republican Party, June 8, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 184)
- North Dakota Trip, June 3-4, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 185)
- NAR Statement: Answer to Nixon; Camden Press Conference, June 9, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 186)
- Brooklyn Sunday School Union - Luncheon and Parade, June 9, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 187)
- British Exhibition Opening - New York City, June 10, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 188)
- New York State Republican Committee - Annual Dinner - New York City, June 14, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 189)
- Roswell Park Memorial Institute - Dedication of New Basic Science Building - Buffalo, New York, June 17, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 190)
- National Sunday School and Baptist Training Union - Baptist Convention - Buffalo, New York, June 17, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 191)
- San Juan Baptista Celebration - Randalls Island, New York City, June 19, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 192)